这里就是testLocationTable方法
Here's what the testLocationTable method looks like.
首先  我们获取一个可写数据库的引用
First, we grab a reference to a writable database
这是因为我们要修改数据库
because we'll be modifying the database.
然后我们使用TestUtilities类中的方法
Then we create content values for
创建一行位置信息的ContentValues对象
a row of location data using the function within test utilities.
接着把这个ContentValues对象插入到位置表中
Then we insert that content values object into the location table.
插入语句的返回值是这一行的id字段
The return value of the insert statement should be row ID.
如果返回值是-1  说明插入操作失败了  我们需要对此断言
If it's negative one, we know the insertion failed, so we assert that.
然后我们只传入表名参数进行数据查询
Then we query the location table and pass in null for all the parameters
这会得到所有行和列的默认查询结果集
to get a default query of all tabled rows and columns, since we want
这么做是因为我们想要确认数据库中的所有数据都是我们插入的
a precisely verify that our database only contains our inserted record.
查询操作会返回一个Cursor对象
The query will return a cursor.
这里我们断言不能将Cursor对象指向第一行数据（也就是查询结果为空）
And we are assert if we cannot move it to the first row.
最后  我们调用TestUtilities中的validateCurrentRecord方法验证
Finally, we call validate current record from the test utility to validate
查询的结果是否正确
the query will return the correct record.
validateCurrentRecord方法会从我们插入的
Validate current record grabs the set of value pairs
ContentValues对象中获得键值对的集合
from the content values that we inserted.
然后遍历这个集合  用Cursor对象的getColumnIndex方法
It then iterates through them, using cursor.getColumnIndex
通过键的名称获得每个键在Cursor中索引值
to get the index of each column in the record set by name.
我们需要通过这个索引值从Cursor对象中读取数据
We need the column index to get data from the cursor.
注意返回的数据的属性顺序和映射数组是一致的
Note the projections are always return in order.
所以如果我们指定了映射数组参数  我们就可以直接使用映射数组
So if we specify a projection, we can safely use the indexes from our
中的索引值  而不需要像这样进行查找
projection array without having to look them up like this.
让我们回到我们的测试
Let's go back to our test.
我们通过断言moveToNext返回false确认数据库中只有一个记录
We checked to make sure the database has only one record by making sure we moved
然后关闭Cursor对象和数据库以保证不会泄漏资源
to next fails, then we close the cursor and database, we don't leak resources.
最后  我们返回locationRowId值
Finally, we return the locationRowId.
运行一下测试看看
Let's run the test and see what happens.
测试通过  只剩下一个测试要写啦
And the test past, [SOUND], only one more test to write.